Neha Sharma Mobile: + 8447862985

E-mail: nehasharma2166.ns@gmail.com

MBA Finance with 9 Years Of Experience In Finance & Accounts

Objective

Being a committed team player, want to be a part of a renowned organization, to contribute towards the growth of the Organization, based on my expertise and to further enhance my personal capabilities by learning from the new Exposure within the structured framework of the organization.

Educational Details

Degree	Board/University	Year Of Passing
MBA (Finance)	Sikkim Manipal University	2015
B.Com.	Delhi University	2011
Higher Secondary	C.B.S.E, Delhi	2008
Senior Secondary	C.B.S.E, Delhi	2006

Work Experience

Organization: India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd.

Company Profile: NBFC

Duration: May 2023 to till date

Designation: Sr. Executive-Finance

Responsibilities –

- Preparing Reports for National Housing Bank (NHB).
- Prepare Incentive Reports-Credit and Technical.
- > Prepare SOP for all reports which we report to NHB
- Review invoices for Appropriate documentation prior to payment
- ➤ Vendor invoice processing with compliance of TDS, GST.
- > Preparation of Vendor Reconciliation on Weekly & Monthly basis.
- ➤ Booking Vendor Invoices & Vendor Payments of Daily Basis.

Organization: Dhani Loans & Services Ltd. (Indiabulls Group)
Company Profile: NBFC

Duration: March 2018 to April 2023
Designation: Sr. Officer Finance & Accounts

Responsibilities -

- ➤ Processing of Rent of more than 200 Branches like Creation Rental object, Release SD and rent to branches, F & F for to close branch, Escalation to Branches for any GST default and other issues. Sent multiple MIS to management and monthly provisions.
- ➤ Booking Vendor Invoices & Vendor Payments of Daily Basis.
- Review invoices for Appropriate documentation prior to payment
- Vendor invoice processing with compliance of TDS, GST.
- Preparation of Vendor Reconciliation on Weekly & Monthly basis.
- > Prepare and Post Clearing of the vendors on monthly basis.
- > Collaborate extensively with auditors during preliminary and year- end audit processes.
- ➤ Ensuring reclassification and accounting of wrong and unaccounted entries prior to Financial year closing.
- ➤ Preparation of Monthly/ Quarterly Provision Detail of Expenses.
- Preparation of MIS Reports for Management.
- > Preparation Bank Reconciliation.

Organization: Design Dialogues (India) Pvt. Ltd, Delhi. **Duration: Feb 2014 to Feb 2018**

Company Profile: Manufacturing & Service Sector **Designation:** Accounts & Tax Executive

Responsibilities -

- > Day to Day entries of Financial Transactions.
- Monthly Closing Entries.
- > Preparation of Monthly/ Quarterly Tax Computations (Excise, VAT, Service tax)
- > Preparation of MIS Reports for Management.
- > TDS Compliance on Payments.
- > Statutory Record keeping like, RG-1, CENVAT Register, and etc.
- Monthly Bank and Debtors/Creditors reconciliation Statements.
- Assisting Team Members in performing their duties.
- ➤ Handling Work related to statutory forms e.g. C and F Forms, DS-2 Form, etc.

Organization: KK Rubber & Plastic Co. Duration: Sep 2013 to Jan 2014. **Designation:** Accounts Executive

Company Profile: Trading

Responsibilities -

- Maintaining Stock in ERP System.
- > Preparation of Reconciliation Statements.
- > Cash Handling and Voucher preparation.

Computing and Analytical Skills

- MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, Gmail and Microsoft Outlook
- > SAP FICO & REFX, Tally ERP 9
- > Using advance Excel formula for MIS like Vlooup, If, Sumif, Sumifs, Pivot table etc.

Personal Details

Father's Name: Sushil Sharma Mother's Name: Suman Sharma

Gender: Female 28th July 1991 Date of Birth: Marital Status: Married

Language Known: English & Hindi

Address: 912/3, Gali No.3, Rajiv nagar,

Gurgaon-122001

Hobbies: Travelling & Listing Music

Winning attitude and Team Player. Strengths:

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the above given place information are true at best of my knowledge.

Date:

Place: New Delhi (Neha Sharma)